{
  "name": "Two letter words",
  "cards": [
    {
      "questionText": "A",
      "answerText": "A"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "B",
      "answerText": "B"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "C",
      "answerText": "C"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "D",
      "answerText": "D"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "E",
      "answerText": "E"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "F",
      "answerText": "F"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "G",
      "answerText": "G"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "H",
      "answerText": "H"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "I",
      "answerText": "I"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "J",
      "answerText": "J"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "K",
      "answerText": "K"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "L",
      "answerText": "L"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "M",
      "answerText": "M"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "N",
      "answerText": "N"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "O",
      "answerText": "O"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "P",
      "answerText": "P"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Q",
      "answerText": "Q"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "R",
      "answerText": "R"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "S",
      "answerText": "S"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "T",
      "answerText": "T"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "U",
      "answerText": "U"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "V",
      "answerText": "V"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "W",
      "answerText": "W"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "X",
      "answerText": "X"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Y",
      "answerText": "Y"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Z",
      "answerText": "Z"
    }
  ]
}
